module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'The word February is derived from the name Februa, a Festival of Purification for the ______',
    a: 'Vikings',
    b: 'Atreides',
    c: 'Greeks',
    d: 'Romans',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'January and February were added to the Roman 10-month calendar last because the Romans....',
    a: 'just wished it was spring already, man.',
    b: 'considered winter a monthless period.',
    c: 'believed the number 10 to be holy.',
    d: 'were getting to it eventually.',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'February was changed to the 2nd month of the year in 450 BCE. What number was it originally?',
    a: '12th',
    b: '6th',
    c: '3rd',
    d: '1st',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'According to _30 Rock_, Leap Day William emerges every four years to trade children\'s tears for ______',
    a: 'grins',
    b: 'terror',
    c: 'high-fives',
    d: 'candy',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'The area of Hollywood was founded in February of ____.',
    a: '1808',
    b: '1887',
    c: '1923',
    d: '1958',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Hattie McDaniel became the first African American to win an Academy Award in February 1940 for her role in _____.',
    a: 'Gone With The Wind',
    b: 'Casablanca',
    c: 'Pinocchio',
    d: 'Shadow of a Doubt',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'George Washington, age 27, married Martha Dandridge Curtis on Feb 22nd, ____.',
    a: '1730',
    b: '1759',
    c: '1780',
    d: '1801',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'In 1960, The Greensboro Sit In took place in ______, protesting discrimination',
    a: 'Alabama',
    b: 'South Carolina',
    c: 'North Carolina',
    d: 'Georgia',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'February is the only month that can pass without a _______.',
    a: 'full moon',
    b: 'asteroid shower',
    c: 'eclipse',
    d: 'breaking dawn -- part 1',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of these years *was* a leap year?',
    a: '1996',
    b: '2001',
    c: '2002',
    d: '2010',
    answer: 'a'
  },
 ];